Rowland Momoh

< Web Developer />

Website GitHub

SUMMARY

I am an ambitious web developer with a solid foundation in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, NodeJS and NextJS. Adept at translating design concepts into responsive and functional websites. I am keen to contribute creative solutions and to collaborate with a dynamic team to enhance user experiences. I possess strong problem-solving skills and a commitment to staying up to date with emerging web technologies.

PROJECTS

Portfolio Website

- Built a fully responsive portfolio website for myself
- Built using the following technologies; React, SCSS, Typescript, EmailJS, Framer Motion and more.
- View project here

Lama Estate

- Built a real estate website for buying or renting apartments.
- Built using React, Typescript, Tailwind CSS and other technologies.
- View project <u>here</u>

Rock, Paper, Scissors game

- Built a fun rock paper scissors game with HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Showcasing my knowedge on JavaScript, JSON and Local storage.
- View project <u>here</u>

Mortgage Calculator

- Built a fully responsive mortage calculator app with HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Solution to frontend mentor's challenge
- View project <u>here</u>

Dawaki, Abuja

(+234) 80 3820 9794

Email LinkedIn

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript **Proficient**

React (NodeJS, NextJS)

Proficient

Unix, Git,

Average

Problem Solving

Proficient

Effective Communication

Proficient

Teamwork

Proficient

EDUCATION

Kogi State University B.ed in Mathematics

Jan 2016 - Dec 2019

Kogi State, Anyingba

CERTIFICATION

Meta Frontend Developer Professional Certificate

November 2023

HTML and CSS in depth

Programming with JS

Scrimba

December 2023

Learn CSS Grid

Learn CSS Flexbox

Rowland Momoh

IT Support Specialist

Dawaki, Abuja

+234 80 3820 9794

momohrowland@gmail.com LinkedIn Website

Summary

I am an enthusiastic IT support specialist with a solid foundation in hardware/software troubleshooting and a customer-centric approach. A Quick learner, critical thinker and keen to contribute my technical and soft skills to enhance organizational efficiency. I also possess excellent communication and teamwork abilities.

Skills & Competencies

- Troubleshooting and problem solving skills.
- Knowledge of operating systems (Windows, Linux, Mac).
- Effective Communicator
- Web development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node JS).
- Customer service.

Experience

Unique International Academy, Bwari, Abuja Teacher

2020 - 2021

- Taught Information Technology to the Junior Secondary School students.
- Responsible for installing/updating software needed for effective learning.

Bet9ja, Kogi Cashier

2016 - 2019

- Ensured smooth running of the organization and customers' satisfaction.
- Troubleshoot system related problems such as printing and internet connections.

Education & Certification

Google IT Support, Online

SFP 2023 - NOV 2023

• Verify certificate here

Kogi State University, Anyingba B.(ed)

JAN 2016 - DEC 2019

Bachelor of Education Mathematics.